Hey, it's Amanda. Leave a message.
It's Natelie.
Cameron came by the bar tonight.
I thought he was gonna hurt me,
he was in my face.
He was totally out of control,
they had' to kick him out.
You better deal with this.
Good morning.
Detective Ferris, Detective Howe.
Listen, maybe we could just
start with the last time...
...that you saw Natalie, and we'll go
through events one thing at a time.
Lisa! I'm open!
It's me again. This can't be happening.
My car's dead. It's not starting.
I'm stuck on the side of the road, like,
I don't know, five miles from the bar.
I need you to come get me.
Why aren't you answering your phone?
Where are you?
The third factor is outcomes:
The results of these trategies
in action.
We're not just
making predictions here
...not just what we think
is going to happen...
...but what are all the other
possible things that don't happen?
If we want to understand, say...
Amanda. Hold on.
Wait. Wait a minute.
If you need someone to talk to
I mean..
...I could be that person.
You're a really good friend, Mark.
I'll be okay.
It's just a room
It has nothing to do with Natalie.
I can't afford to pay
for an empty room anymore
Can you?
-Hey, I'm Zoe.
-Hey, Hailey.
-Nice to meet you.
-Yeah, you too.
- Hailey.
- Amanda
Nice to meet you.
-So this is your first year?
-Yeah.
What do you want to study?
Well, I grew up on a farm,
and I work in an animal hospital
...so I've been thinking
about vet sciences.
So this is it.
TV room, cable, DVD player.
The fireplace works,
but we have to go easy on the wood
...because the ashes can get messy.
My room
Amanda's.
And...
this would be your room
It's great.
Hey!
Hi.
I made you some tea
Thanks.
It looks nice.
Yeah.
So have you had a chance
to check out campus?
Little bit. I got the basic tour
back in spring.
Well, if you want,
I can show you around.
I appreciate the offer, but it's okay.
Look, there are
some really cool places...
...I'm sure that they
didn't show you.
Sure.
Great.
I heard about Klein. That's amazing.
Who's Klein?
Maria Klein.
She's like all over the news
about that DNA databank thing.
Yeah, Amanda interned
at her office all summer...
...and now she's got a big job
lined up after she graduates.
Where'd you hear about that?
Everyone's heard about that
Klein's a big deal.
What?
Does she know?
Know what?
Natalie was my friend.
She lived in your room.
I'm living in a dead girl's room?
She is missing.
Nobody said she was dead.
Look, I'm sorry.
Maybe we should've said something
Forget it.
It's just a room, right?
I'm gonna go.
Yeah, it was nice to meet you
and I'll see you later.
She used to make us do
the craziest things.
This one time my freshman year,
I was having a hard time.
You know, school, boys...
My parents were always away.
Natalie knew this. Anyway, she
woke us up at the crack of dawn...
...and she shoves us in the car
She drives us to the country...
...and doesn't tell us where we're going.
She booked a whitewater rafting trip.
I was terrified. I mean, I was afraid--
I was scared of the water,
the raft, drowning...
Fucking bitch knew it too.
But she had a way about her.
You know, it's like--
It's like that she knew
what was good for you
So did you do it?
It was the best trip of my life.
She was one of those girls,
you know?
No matter what
you were going through
...or how shitty life was...
.when she was around
everything was okay.
I remember seeing her
in the papers and everything.
I never really paid
much attention though
What happened?
Natalie was a waitress
at The Black Swan.
She worked one morning till 2 a.m...
and that was the last time
anybody saw her.
We put up posters, talked to
people in the bar that night...
...read the papers,
followed the news.
Just trying to fit
the pieces together, you know?
Sometimes I even go to that spot
where her car was found...
...and try to imagine what happened.
Every scenario in my head is bad.
Hey.
Like you said, she's missing.
She could still be alive.
How've you been?
Haven't seen you in a while.
How's your new place?
Fine.
You gonna stay for dinner?
I went shopping.
I have to go
Mom said I could have it.
If you need money, just ask.
Wait.
Take it.
Look, I just want to talk, okay?
Figure this out.
There's nothing to talk about.
Look, I fucked up, Okay?
I know that...
...but we're supposed to be together.
You said that, you remember?
I was wrong.
Now move.
Move!
Amanda, please believe me.
I had nothing to do with Natalie!
Don't make me say it again.
Hey!
Hey, you guys are leaving already?
Yeah, so excited.
Have a good weekend.
Thanks. See you later.
--Pacify certain interests
in the country...
...Maria Klein's announcement
last week effectively killed...
legislation that would have
seen the creation...
...of a nationwide DNA databank
for missing persons.
By allowing jurisdictions to opt out...
...well, this makes the databank
next to useless before it's even started.
Meanwhile, the families
of missing persons...
... continue to suffer
and continue to wonder. .
...whether their loved ones
have been found and not identified.
- For this reason...
- Klein?
...I am not supporting this legislation.
Yeah.
Are you worried
people are going to blame you.-
...for this not going through?
My message to them,
and Mn Shaughnessy, is this:
Do it right, or don't do it at all.
The families of missing people,
they deserve better.
Hey, that's you.
Yeah, that was like a week ago.
What did you do for her?
A lot of things.
Primarily, I watched her back,
till this happened.
One of her rivals backpedaled
on some legislation...
...and I was the one who caught it.
Next thing I knew we were
in front of the cameras.
You look good.
--legislation that was ill-conceived
and full of loopholes from the get-go.
It was never going to see
the light of day.
If I hadn't revealed it when I did,
someone else would have.
If people want to blame me
for its failure, they can go ahead.
What?
Nothing.
The questions people
should be asking are...
why were jurisdictions given
the option to opt out?
And why wasn't it mandatory...
---for all law-enforcement agencies
to participate?
It's a major setback, but I don't intend
to let this die a quiet death.
Hey.
Sony, I thought I heard someone.
I don't hear anything.
Oh, for chrissake.
When are you gonna get it
through your thick skull?
We're done. Now get the fuck away
from me, or I'm calling the police.
I love you
I always will. Don't you see?
Hey, get your fucking
hands off her! Get off her!
- Who the fuck are you?
- Come here, jerk-off. You'll find out
Listen, bitch, this doesn't
fucking concern you--
Fuck!
Fuck you!
I can't believe I ever got
mixed up with that guy.
He was one of the last people
to ever see Natalie alive.
He was there that night at the bar.
I know he had something to do with it.
I can't prove it, I just
I just know.
I told the cops, but they
couldn't do anything about it
The guy's sick.
He's obsessed.
I don't think he's ever gonna stop.
Gotta go.
Get the fuck back here!
Bitch!
No! No!
Get off of me!
Get off me!
He has a gun
Fuck you
No! No!
The cops will never believe
it was self-defense.
Amanda.
Think about Natalie, okay?
The police did nothing.
We can do this.
Now help me.
Hey.
Don't worry
No one's home.
Zoe's not home yet, so that's good.
It's over.
Never happened.
Say it.
Say it again.
It never happened.
Hi, I have some information
about a dead body.
On a farm.
Yeah, it might be that
missing girl, Natalie Ross
Garret Jones?
You mind if we ask you
a few questions?
What's that over there?
I don't know.
- Detective!
- Excuse me.
All I can tell you is
a male between the ages of 20 and 28
No teeth, no fingerprints.
His face is destroyed.
lD'ing this guy's gonna be a bitch
Anything else?
My guess, it could be a mob hit.
My property's 115 acres
with access to three different roads
Anyone can drive in there
...kick open a gate and dump
whatever the hell they want.
Just because a body's
found on my property/..
...doesn't mean I had
anything to do with it.
- Oh, we got your ax.
- You got someone's ax
You got my fingerprints on it?
No. And you know how I know?
Because it's not mine.
So if you have any evidence
linking me to this crime...
...I'd love to hear it.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
Found a set of tire tracks...
...out near where the body was found.
Now, it doesn't match your vehicle...
...or anything else on your property.
Any idea whose vehicle
those tracks belong to?
Not a clue.
A local man was taken in for questioning today...
...after human remains
were found on his farm.
Police were led to believe the body
was Natalie Ross...
the girl who mysteriously disappeared
four and a half months ago-
But police confirmed the body
was an unidentified male.
The death is being treated
as a homicide-
No charges have been laid.
Holy fuck.
Hailey, we're in a lot of trouble.
Oh, my God
What happened?
My dad dropped by for a little visit.
Your dad?
What?
I called the cops.
Wha--? You called the cops?
Why would--?
Why would you do that?
Are you fucking crazy?
Shit!
Hailey, they can identify the body...
...and trace it back to us.
Why would you do that?
Why?!
Because the son of a bitch
killed my mom.
My dad used to beat the shit
out of my mom on a daily basis.
I grew up watching her
take it and take it.
The last few years she had nothing left.
She was just a fucking zombie.
I woke up one morning
and she was dead.
Officially, it was a suicide...
...but I know it was him.
And then he moved on to me.
I was lucky this time,
because he was sober.
And he's gonna get to drinking again
like he always does...
...and he's gonna think
about what I tried to do to him...
...and it's gonna screw in his brain
and he's gonna come back...
and he's gonna kill me
There's a way...
...that we can fix everything.
We solve both of our problems.
We kill him.
What?
We can pin it on my dad so the cops
think my dad killed Cameron.
Okay? There's no trail
leading back to us.
I can't listen to this.
Look at what he did!
I killed for you...
...now you kill for me
You're sick.
Can I stay here with you?
Of course.
What's going on?
What happened?
Well, what are we talking about here?
Trouble at school?
-No.
-Pregnant?
No.
Are we talking about something illegal?
Yes
I got myself
involved in something...
..and I don't know
how to get myself out.
What are the chances you get caught?
I don't-- I don't know.
It's a little difficult to give you advice.
All right, let me ask you this.
Have you learned from this mistake?
Yes. Yes, absolutely
Show me one person out there
who hasn't done something illegal
I suppose if it were me
...I'd do what I had to do
tpo get out of it...
...without getting caught,
and then I would never do it again
We're just human beings.
You know, we make mistakes.
But we can learn from them.
We don't always need the law...
...be-cause we have
our guilt and our conscience..
...and sometimes
that's more than enough
It'll be okay.
Why are you doing this?
I'm so glad that you called.
There's something
that I have to tell you
Hello?
Mark?
I think you should come home.
We need to talk.
- What the fuck did you do?
- Well, I think that's pretty obvious
You didn't really
leave me much of a choice.
You're fucking out of your mind.
Oh, you're fucking crazy.
Holy shit. Where is he?
Calm down, he's fine.
Who you calling?
You calling the police?
Okay.
But remember that I still have the ax...
...and it has your fingerprints all over it.
"Officer, it's wasn't me.
Why would I kill him?
I mean, it's her ex-boyfriend
I guess they got in a fight
and when he wasn't looking...
...she put an ax
in the back of his head."
Pop!
You fucking bitch!
Do it!
I don't wanna hurt Mark...
...so don't make me hurt Mark.
Fuck, Amanda...
...you're free
I just want the same thing.
Help me and we both
get what we want.
I can't kill your dad.
It's Mark or my dad.
You're going to kill somebody.
He'll be at the bar till they kick him out.
Give me that.
How do you know that's enough?
Internet.
Apparently it's sweet.
It doesn't taste that bad.
Put that under the sink.
Who the fuck is that?
It's just someone turning around.
Happens all the time.
Okay, printer works, lots of ink
We're set.
This is where Natalie worked.
Like clockwork.
She's not gonna go.
That's exactly what you'll do.
Only you're gonna get in that truck.
I'm a murderer who can
no longer live with myself.
That's what the note should say.
Keep it short and sweet.
Print it off his computer,
get his fingerprints on it...
...and after you're done
wipe everything down.
Don't touch anything.
Hey. Hey!
Remember, he's a crafty son of a bitch
He's fucking smart.
You have to stay one step
ahead of him the entire time.
Look.
We can do this.
Okay, this is a good thing
that we're doing.
It may not seem like it now.
-What can I get you?
-Can I get a beer, please?
Yeah , you bet.
Okay, so I sign here?
Great.
I didn't know you were in tonight.
I switched with Marie.
I'll need you to get Mrs. Newlander some
Meloxicam, the 8-milligram tablets.
She's out in the waiting room.
They're not doing too good, are they?
Excuse me. Can I get
a tequila sunrise, please?
Yup. You bet
You want one?
On me.
No, thanks, I'm not really a big fan...
...of those sweet and fruity cocktails.
Come on.
Can't knock it till you try it.
You might change your mind.
What's your name?
Aren't you a little young
to be honing in on me?
I'm older than I look.
No, you're not
What are you drinking?
Doesn't have a name.
Just like you.
What's in it?
Half glass beer,
quarter glass whiskey...
...quarter glass 7-Up
That's a cocktail.
No, it ain't.
A cocktail has
two or more ingredients in it
and one of them has to be a spirit
A whiskey's a spirit, so that, my friend...
-...is a cocktail
- Yeah'?
What are you, cocktail police?
It's not bad. For a cocktail.
For the lady.
Try it
Well?
Do I know you?
You can still change your mind.
If Mo shows any signs of distress
give her another painkiller.
Okay.
-Are you sure you're okay?
-I'm fine.
Is that your daughter?
Yeah. That's Hailey.
She's pretty
She is that, all right.
She gets her good looks
from her mama.
I can see some of you in her
Where is she now?
She moved away.
She doesn't come around here
much anymore except when she
...need to steal something
for money.
The kid's pretty messed up.
What do you mean?
She hurts herself.
Cuts.
Bruises.
I don't know why
One time she threw herself
down a flight of stairs.
The poor kid looked like
she was in a car wreck.
Her and her mom
didn't really get along.
There was a lot
of friction there so
Maybe that's when it started.
When her mom died...
When she died...?
She committed suicide.
She poisoned herself,
which is a horrible way to go
I've never told anyone
There was something about it
that just wasn't right.
You can tell me.
She left a suicide note...
...and it blamed me for...
...basically everything.
The thing was printed off the computer.
I was married to that woman
for 16 years...
...and I never once saw her
use that computer.
Sometimes I think about...
...stalling over again.
Finding a new woman
to share my life with...
...have another kid.
Try and do it right this time.
We never do get a second chance...
to fix the big fuck-ups
in our lives, do we?
No. No, we don't
So, what's this fruity
concocotion of yours, hus?
Does that have a name?
We're through.
Do you understand me?
It's over.
I want details.
I want every single detail.
Don't leave anything out.
I don't know where else
they would've come from.
But they popped up and stalled--
They started grabbing me and I...
I don't know. I don't even know
if it was a man or a woman.
I was wondering if you
could do me a favor.
I've tried calling my dad
and there's no answer.
I'm stuck at school
and I can't make it there
ls there any way you can check
on him since you live so close?
Yeah, I could do that.
Great. Is there any way you could
go today? I'm getting kind of worried.
Sure, I'll head there now.
Thanks.
- Hello'?
- Hailey, hi.
It's Mrs. Farnsworth.
I went over to check on your dad'.--
---and I knocked on the door
but there was no answer.
The door was locked
so I just looked around.--
...but I didn't see anything.
I mean, his truck was in the driveway.
Maybe he's gone hunting-
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Hailey?
- Drive.
- Get out
We're gonna go for a little ride.
Get out of my car!
What do you want?
Look at me.
Drive.
Drive!
This is fucking crazy.
Where is he?
I don't know.
That's fucking bullshit!
Maybe he crawled off
and died somewhere.
Wait. Don't drink.
I have to tell you something.
About your daughter.
You know my daughter?
Yeah.
What are we gonna do?
You do what you came here to do-
You carry out your plan
Did you get it?
Good.
How do you know she'll come?
I know my daughter.
What are you gonna do?
The girl needs help.
I'm gonna see she gets it.
New get the fuck out of here
and never come back.
Go!
Amanda!
Get in the hole.
Go on.
Get in there! Get in there!
Get in the fucking hole!
Look what you made me do
We're free.
Amanda?
Natalie.
Who's that?
That's his daughter.
He told me his family was dead.
Said he wanted to start a new one.
Come on.
Let's go
911. What's your emergency?
We need an ambulance.
I found her.
Natalie Ross.
What's the address?
We're at the end
of Little Mountain Road.
I don't know the number.
The police have been here before.
Last month they found a body
in the woods.
I was involved in that.
I knew him.
His name was Cameron McClure.
I helped bury him.
Ma'am?
Ma 'am, are you still there?
Yes, I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere.